Downloaded @ subs4free.club
Quiet!
What are you?
You're a demon!
No, I'm not a demon
See, I'm just guy
Here to rescue these dragons, so uh!
But you walked through fire!
Dragon scale, Dragon shatterlocks.
I know a demon when I see one
No human legs can last in it
Think that is a good entrance!
You get a lot of me
More demons!
It's just neat way to forget to fireproof his butt
Hot! Hot hot hot!
Guys, no! Not yet!
Behold, your worst nightmare!
Behold!
I'm a sister who insisted i'm coming
- Thats my intro,
- Guys too soon.
You always come in too soon
Sorry! I'm still getting hang of my wings
Fishleg, Again with a baby?
This is a raid
I couldn't find a sitter.
Demons everywhere! This is the end of the world!
Astrid, I had him right where I wanted him
And now he is right where I wanted him!
- Let's get to work
- Okay, we screwed that up
But, at least nobody knows that we're here
Easy girl, It's okay
We'll gonna get you out of here
The Crimson Coregutter
Look at this wierdo! That's super dumb!
Why can't I get this cage open
Its Slides,
- Obviously!
- Attack!
Get the rescues out of here
No running on the deck, its slippery!
You can fall
Step Aside!
Let me handle the tough guy stuff
That's 2 for me
Look out!
Sorry
Thank you
Now! Go to the other rest of our
I thought this was suppose to be a stealth mission
Yeah, they always start that way!
Thank you, Stormfly!
Stop worrying they'll get it.
Eventually
Move out! We got them all
I am gonna handlock every last one of you.
I might even headlock you
Amateurs, It just getting started
Clear up Guys! Go! Go!
Good hustle boys!
Toothless, time to go!
Hey Guys!
You always have my back right!?
This is Berk
Your new home away from home
A stunning one stop all expense paid
dream destination
So settle in and let your worries melt away
The service here is sourced,
The cuisine is fiery
And the locals are as colourful as you get
Any run of the mill paradise boasts
beaches and sunshine
But not us
We have something that no one else can touch
We my friend, have dragons!
Lots and lots of dragons!
And meet our latest Berkins
Welcome to paradise, meat!?
You're a beauty
You're welcome
I took on like a 100 trappers...
a 1000 trappers
With his own burning undies
My thick full beard almost caught on fire
Just. Just Stop!
So, Hiccup's mom, do you know it's my bone crashing assault
or is it pretty much perfect
It was indescribable
And please call me Valka. It has been a year
First name basis!
I think the real hero of the day was Toothless
Is that right bud
What would we do without you, King of Dragons
What would we do?!
Well! We could train a lot harder for one
That was pretty sloppy
Astrid does have a point
The actual, we rely a little bit to much on your dragons
and not enough for one another
See, that's what exactly what I was saying
just listen up guys
Yeap! Your mom is super impressed with me
I'm like the son she always wanted
Fishmeal!
You found a new friend
Watch your heads!
What good
is having the King of Dragons around,
if he can't keep the order
Hey bud! You want to do something here or
and where do you suppose we put these ones
We'll make room
You brought back a Hobgobbler
They're bad omen. We're cursed!
Nonsense
What harm can he do?!
No injuries, in all a little shaken
but in otherwise healthy
Now, who's hungry
The point is you can't keep
bringing dragons back here
- Come on boy
- You just asking for trouble
Who's trouble is getting closer by the day
We can handle them. We have the Alpha.
Ain't that right bud
Would you look how happy they are!
She's Awesome!
Gobber, relax. We did it!
The world 1st dragon-viking utopia
We made the dream a reality
Your dream, maybe
mine is less crowded and more
Sanitary!
Gobber, You're not fooling anybody
I know you love them
You supposed to be the generation
that leads us to the future
Food Fight!
Gorgeous!
Watch the hair!
Good fish meat! Am nom nom nom!
God help us
Try to stop worrying about the problems out there,
and start sorting out the ones right here!
Ok ok! I think we got it
Hang up your saddles and get married
- The M word
- Gross, unless its me
Start ruling like a proper royal couple
Marry him please,
you're the only one with any sense around here
- With you waiting the pads, there still hope
- Woah!
- Gobber
- Not awkward at all!
Astrid, don't be like that
Whew! That is a definitive no!
Look! If you need a beard to cry on?!
Just lean on my shoulder and you
can cry on my full thick beard
Thank you, Tuffnut. Thank you... so much
Eret, son of Eret What is the report
Two more trapper budges spotted in the straight
So we go after them
What!?
One day you gonna pick a fight
you can't win
Archers!
Deathgrippers
The dragon raiders attacked us here,
of the Eastern Straight
Ragnar Rock!
Sorry
My dear Warlords, how go your plans
to conquer the world
Grimmel, my old friend. Thank you for coming!
A year since Drago's defeat
and no following along your dragon army I see
You can thank the young chief of Berk for that
Storik's boy
He and his peace loving dragon riders
continue to raid our ships
and steal our dragons
That does sound like a nuisance
But i'm in a business of killing dragons,
not retrieving them
But, Grimmel
That idiot boy who has done all for you
Gathering the dragons in one place
Why bothers me
Because the flock is protected by a Night Fury
That's not possible
It seems one slipped through your fingers
Look Berk's dragons will follow the Alpha
So we will pay you to capture him
and bring the flock to us
We even have your favourite paid
The only dragon they left us
from the last night's raid
A female?!
So, do we have a deal? Old friend
When all the seven done, this young chief
will bring me Night Fury
They don't have a leader,
just a boy
Hiccup
This is Berk, son
it's our home
It was a home of your grandparents'
house and your grandparents before them
It is my job as Chief to protect us, Hiccup
And one day, when you all grown up
- That job will be passed on to you
- Ok
And it's very important, son, because out there,
beyond the sunset,
- Lies the home of the dragons
- Wow!
Legend tells of ships that sailed too close to it
only to drop off the edge of the world,
never to be seen again
But those sailors who turned back
told tales of a great waterfall
and dragons guarding the entrance
into the hidden world
Not just a nest, Hiccup
but a line from which all the dragons come
Even Night Furies
Especially Night Furies.
Those are scary
Don't you worry!
One day I'll find the Hidden World,
and seal the top
so that people and dragons
will fight no more
What?
Oh, all right, you do know
its not a chew toy don't you?
Is this what you want!
Do you want this leg! Do you want my leg
Go get it!
Getting pretty good at gliding on your own bud
So this is where you come to get away from Gobber
I have no idea what you're talking about
- Well, he is right you know
- Really?!
- You think you and I should
- Oh Gods no
- We're no where near ready for that
- No, That's crazy
I mean, he's right about all of this
It does seem like the whole world knows about us now
Yep, and the more dragons we bring back here,
the bigger of a target we become
I just wish there is some way
that will make them leave us alone
there might be
Dad used to talk about old mariners myth
of a secret land at the edge of the world
where dragons lived totally out of reach
- Well, sailors are know for tall tales
- True
But what if its real
It could be the answer to all of our problems
How?
By Moving the dragons there?
Uh uh! All of us
Seriously?!
And abandon our home with 7 generations
- The home your father left you to protect
- (Sigh) Uh
Yeah, I think we need a real solution, Hiccup
Or we can just take Gobber's advice and tie the knot
That should fix everything
But hey, if you're having doubts about yours truly
I'm pretty sure Snotlout is available
He only has eyes for your mom
- Playing dirty now, huh
- You asked for it
Looks like there might be a wedding after all
Woah!
How dare you, that was a low blow. No no
You're not getting away
Okay okay, you win! You win!
You always win
- You know what we are getting into
Aha! Right
Uh! Bud!
Wait! Yeah, sure, don't bother to wait for us (Sigh)
OMGs!
Hiccup!
Yeah, we are friends. You do not need to kill us
- Woah!
- Another Night Fury
No not quite its more like a ... Bright Light Fury
- A Light Fury
Yeah, yours is better, probably
- What do you mean gone
- Vanished into thin air
What do you think?
- Uh uh
- Stubbier ears, no dorsal plates
- Uh huh, okay, got it!
Huh huh! What a night
What! What's getting into you
What is all this slobbering and panting
Isn't it obvious, he is in love
Trust me, relationships are nothing but pain and misery
What did I just say!
Am I not enough?
I think thats a "no"
Something like this?
You know what!
Just trace a toothless card and make her white
- You could have let with that
- Can you believe it!
- Toothless has a girlfriend!
- I never took you for a romantic, like ever.
But it's so sweet, I mean, Look!
Okay, that's just sad
- And weird.
- Yeah, you better do something
Seriously, I'd rather shovel poop all day than watch that
Alright, let's head back to the woods and see if we can find her
- Ah! Got an idea, a little private fee
- Ah
Its boy talk, come on, let's go work this out
- Uh! What?
- So, you want to get married?
- Uh! No, actually...
Good news, I've been to 2 weddings
I've crashed both but
none as hight profile as this one
Lots of pressure, judgment and not just by me
Look! We talked about it. We're not getting married.
Hold feet, I've seen it before
Don't worry little Hickie, i'm here
Wait! Hickie
Now, i've seen the way that
Astrid looks at you
Everyone has that doubt
That not so settle disappointment,
that longing for something more than you
You need to focus on being worthy
I mean, she's a warrior... queen for Thor's sake
and you are neither
But with me, as your best man.
Your spirit guide if you will
You will learn to embrace your inner viking
Show the nay sayers, are which there are many
that you are more than just a mo-nourish runt
with bad hair, strange teeth,
and a twig for a neck
You're... you're really bad at pep talks
Stop letting this insecurity get the best of you
Everyone's watching.
I mean everyone. You need to man up!
Do as I do, it will be hard
but you have my word
And I die brake that word, I won't give up
Hey!
My time here
you see some shiny things in the woods and
What is that?
Toothless!
Don't move a muscle
Hey!
Someone's here, he managed to slip passed our scouts
And lay a trap in the woods
It ruined boy talk
- Let me got em
- Slow down Gobber
Let's get a search team on the ground
scouts in the air
Toothless and I will fly the coastline
Yeah! I wouldn't advice taking Toothless anywhere chief
I know this handy work
Grimmel The Grizzly
Famous back where I'm from
The smartest dragon hunter I've ever met
Well, next to me, of course
He can not be that smart. He left his trap on land
Haha! Nothing is accidental when it comes to old Grimmel
He lives for the hunt
to get inside the mind of his prey
to control each every choice
Its all a game to him
Well, he doesn't know who he's playing with
Yes, and we've dealt with this kind of guy before
Don't underestimate him, Hiccup
Mark my words, he will be back
Then we'll be waiting for him
Come on, Give me a clue here
Gimme a clue Dad
Oh! I hope you do not mind if I help myself
This is quite good
That is impressive, but let me finish my drink
Toothless!
What did you do to him?
Nothing that he won't slip off
Ah! Haha! May i
Chief Hiccup, huh!
Do I say Chief Hiccup, or do I call you Hiccup
What do you prefer?
You have no idea who I am, do you?
Huh
Well, Your father know of me
Now, there was a Chief
One of the greatest dragon hunters to have ever lived
What would he think of you?
He had it right you know
Making it his mission to destroy the beasts
so that you can grow into a better world
He changed his mind
Look where that got him
So let's get to the point
I'm the Night Fury killer
I hunted every last one but yours
You are going to give me that dragon
- Or I will...
- I will never give him up
You wish dragons to live free among us
like equal
A toxic notion my boy
History has shown that we are superior species
What if word of your misguided ideas where to spread
It would be the undoing of the
civilisation as we know it
Did we get him?
Now!
Sorry to barge in
You think you can come into my home, sit in my father's chair,
and threaten my dragon
This is Berk
And we've defended our way of life
from far worst than you
A Fighting spirit I love it. Only
I'm afraid you're mistaken
You've never seen anything like me
Astrid, look out!
Look out!
Son Get Clear
Have my dragon ready when I return
Or I will destroy everything you love
Alright everybody, settle down pls!
Fishlegs, have you ever seen
that species of dragon before
Let me had him!
I give it a piece of my mind
And my mind I mean fist
Did you miss the part where we almost died
Have you seen my house
This is a new kind of enemy and I underestimated him
Now that's on me
but I will not do that again
We're vikings, we don't run from a fight
At least, I don't. You might
I agree with Hiccup
We haven't seen the last of Grimmel
He is a predator. A single minded and patient
He won't stop until he gets what he wants
I agree with Eret
We have to take this threat seriously
Grimmel is just a sign of the times
Our enemies are getting smarter, more determined
We are not just overcrowded, we are exposed and vulnerable
Short of full blown war and risking everyone we love
I don't
I don't see a way of staying here for any longer
This is bull...
Hey!
Hear him out!
If we want to live in peace with our dragon,
- we need a better plan
- So what are you saying chief
I'm saying we have to disappear
Off the map
Take the dragons to a place where no one will find them
And where might that be?
He's talking about the quest for the hidden world
A hidden what?
Out to lunch!
My father was obsessed with it when I was a boy
He made notes and maps in search
of the ancestral homes
of all dragons
Tucked away somewhere beyond the edge of the world
It may be the solution we need
We are dragon people. It's where we belong
Look! I know this is our home
My father left me to protect it
But Berk is more than this place
We are Berk, the people, the dragons
I say Berk is wherever we go
I am with him! Who else?
Excuse me! Coming through, just getting my food here
Wish me luck eat your rocks. Eat your rocks!
Gods, people who fly with the babies were the worst
I feel like I'm always asking you this question, but
We've got to meet up
Is this an actual plan or
Just keep flying until we reach the end of the world
Da, seems sensible
- So, where are they?
- Gone obviously
The Night Fury escaped you? Again?
I encouraged it
They've abandoned their only defensible position
Running scared with what little they can carry
- Just keeps going
- That's cause the world is actually round
Sun is round, moon is round, stars are round
- Even though they're small and stupid
- Right stars
Don't fret, they won't get far
The Night Fury is distracting them
I introduced him to your female
Furies mate for life you see
What you picking up on bud?
- The Light Fury
- She's following us
Hold on Toothless!
Well look who it is!?
Hey! Its really nice to finally me...
Not a word
Yeah yeah, yes, but where did they go?
Explains
Night Furies can't survive in the cold so they haven't gone North
They trying to put distance between themselves
and enemies to the east and south
And Night Furies cannot fly long distances without rest
Their flights paths must include stops
Party break!
Therefore, they've gone...
They can only have gone..
Does anyone want to take a guess?
Anyone?
East!
West!
Simple, you see
Isn't this fun.
Yes!
No
Yes Yes
Where is your love of the hunt
I thought you were conquerors
You'll have your prize in time
Just allow me a few more days to enjoy this
I have dearly missed it
All right, it looks like we're camping here tonight
- Well, thank Thor for that!
- Yes my own place
I planned to build a hut only for the bearded
Ruffnut, you gonna stay out
Chin whiskers don't count
I saw the tower of manliness in the shape of me
Its gonna be taller than Eret with bigger muscles
- What?
- Get out of my house!
- Is there problem here
- Yeah! There's a problem
Ever since you showed up, you been trying to upstage me
You're just so jealous, its delusional
Yeah, delusion is a good word for it
Listen, son of Eret
When Hiccup blows as a chief, I'm next in line
Number two because
I'm clearly Valka's favourite
So you better start showing me some respect
- Strange little man
- Don't mind him
It is not your fault that you
have the body of a northern god
I myself have the same problem
Yeah!
Blacksmith stall goes right here
1, 2, 3, 4, 5 What?
Okay, hold on gang, I said, make camp
- Did you see them?
- Not build a new village
Who died and makes you chief
What?
Granted, This place is very nice,
but this it's not the hidden world
We don't even know if...
this hidden world even exists
Yes, this place is real
There is nothing more stubborn
than a mob of tired, hungry Vikings
Huh! Well, I guess this could work
as a base in the meantime
Its defensible, hidden
Alright! You could stay
Say Hello to the new Berk
Let's get building lads
Until Toothless and I found the Hidden World
Now about that voice
Can we loose the whole honking goose thing
Tired to imagine wedded bliss
with that going up every minute. Eheheh!
If you're going to continue west, I should head back
to make sure we weren't followed
- Great idea I'll go with you for protection
- No!
- You're far too important here
- Yeah
Just be careful
What?
The plan to hide us from the rest of the world
Though I wish it were possible,
I fear it can't last, Hiccup
Well, You know I've tried to do the same for years
But greedy humans always find a way
I just, I only ask that you think about it
Do you still think I'm crazy, or...
Let's just say, this whole idea is very you
Well, Thank you for supporting me last night.
That meant a lot
Don't thank me yet
I just hope you're right about this
Toothless, no its too early
Now you can draw
Someone has not slept
Yeah! Well that Light Fury wont
let me within a mile of her
and neither of us will be getting any sleep
or find the Hidden World
until Toothless takes over
Hey!
What do you think of that?
- Yeah!
- You've tried that once before. He didn't want it
Well, until now he didn't have a reason to
Right bud?
- What?
- No nothing. I'm... I'm impressed
I mean look at you embracing change, I'm proud of you
Well, he is my best bud. I want him to be happy
and besides, it's just until he brings her back
Alright! Fire when ready
Well, I guess you know the tail is fire proof
Okay, Toothless
Yes I know, Shh! Okay, I know
Please this is not helping
Well, well, well, someones is excited
Fresh of his first date
He's in love crazy
Only we are the ones who going crazy
The sooner he brings back that Light Fury, the better
Yeah but to do that, he'll need to fly without me
So time to give this new and improved baby a shot
Atta boy! Lookin' sharp Toothless!
So What do you think bud?
Bring her home. By sundown at the latest
No, Save it for your girlfriend
Go on, get out of here
Its okay
Watch out!
Go, Cloudjumper!
To the chief
Okay, guys now I'm just getting sick
You'll see, I thought you were well off your record
but this spot ain't half bad
This suppose to be a temporary solution
Its unanimous, everyone agrees we've definitely traded it up
Well done Chief
What if the tail is broken
What if Grimmel found him
- What if he needs me?
- Would you relax?
He's probably having the time of his life
How would I know? She never comes around
And when she does, she always rushing off
I'm saying, how would we know if she's right for us?
- Us?
- You know what I mean
She's so wild and skittish
I'm just gonna say it
I don't trust her
God team of all, Hiccup.
One day you'll have to snip those apron strings
and let Toothless stretch his wings
Reminds me of a talk I had
with Stoic about you
Where did they keep coming from?
- Who?
- Those bloody Hobgobblers
I swear they're popping up faster than rabbits
I think they want to eat me
Evidence would suggests I'm tasty
Hicky, a moment
Listen, I've been watching you walk
Loose the limp. No ones gonna marry that
- I have a prosthetic leg
- So am I
Yeah, you are parasitic twin
but you'll not see me limping around about it
Come on! Chin up Hicky, Puff out that chest
Move that butt to the left
Mom, are you hurt? What happened out there?
I don't know how, but Grimmel is tracking us
This is all because of the Hobgobblers
He has hundreds ships, maybe more
With enough cages for all our dragons
If Grimmel is leading them here,
we have to take him out of the mix
And how would we do that?
- By going there and capture him
- Capture him?
I am with him! Who else?
Okay, split up! We will be harder to catch
I was thinking we just split up, just because
I like instincts
What is this?
Quiet!
Where's your dragon when you needed?
Chief?
Must have forgotten all about you?
The first rule of the hunt
Separate the pray from its pack
You just removed yourselves from the equation
- Why are you doing this?
- Really? I do not think you care
Well, unlike you, when I was a boy
and I came up on a Night Fury
I killed him where he slept
That simple act of courage
made me a hero in my village
So I decided to kill every last one
Bringing real peace to the people of this world
Until you came along, preaching that dragons
are something other than thieves and murderers
That nonsense dies now
Starting with you
But you have a dragons of your own
These!?
They are dragon killers
Drugged into obedience with their own venom
Not even your precious Alpha could control them
They serve me, and only me
Allow me to demonstrate
Take cover!
Spread out!
Hurry!
Go go go!
Hiccup!
Got ya!
Let's go, Cloudjumper!
He takes that stupid baby everywhere
- God almighty!
- Guess we won't be needing this thing huh?
- I let us right into his trap
- Yeah nice work, Chief!
Right, Ruff
- Wait... where is Ruffnut?
- We left her behind?
How could you not notice she was missing?
You ride a two-headed dragon
Yeah, I feel like Ruffnut is every day
- Dumb
- Odin be spanked
This just gets better and better
I've tried to avoided looking
right at her gives me ass of reflex
Ok ok guys just keep your helmets on
Toothless and I will...
Toothless has the Light Fury now,
he's probably not even coming back
- What?
- You gave him his freedom, Hiccup. What were you expecting?
I never thought he would stay away for good
I've... I've..
Look I'll figure it out.
I just need more time
He thinks he has to lead alone
Well, Because his father had to
He doesn't realise the strength he have together
- Do you still believe in him
- Of course!
I wished he did
But he thinks he's nothing without Toothless
Then help him realise the truth
- Get on!
- What?
- We are going to find him
- Really!?
Everybody stay put
- We will get Ruffnut back. Don't worry
- Worry?!
If they are stuffed with Ruffnut,
I am more worried about them
Why the long face?
I mean mines long, but yours is really long
All face with no brain, like you got stretched in birth
Do you have a twin too?
Tuffnut took up all the rooms in moms belly
Otherwise I will have a rounder head
and more brains, that's science
My braids are like little zipper bags, see
Yeah! Even the mould spots looks like eyes, so cute
they even have little horns and everything
Just Like Barf and Belch except me and Barf can't stand Belch
So there really just Barfs
Its warm in here
I know what you've thinking
You have never had a prisoner this hot
All the boys love me, except Eret
Who totally lost his chance
That should pass sail boys, Sorry!
And Hiccup is practically married
to that round head Astrid
But it's not loud and officially
so they are basically my inherent
A just getting choosed you know
Its not a lot of beef cake,
but almost too good you know
Sometimes I think he's more
in love with himself than me
There is only room for one beauty
in this relationship
Fishlegs will keep me alive longer
if I had to eat one of them
straight from the glacier somewhere but
He never shuts up about dragons
Don't you hate when people never stop talking
Yes I do
Blah, blah, bla Very boring
Its so boring
Can we just feed her to your dragons
If you have to eat around here,
I'm allergic to fish you should know that
That's all they have on that stupid new island
Too many clams
They are like little mouths with slimy food inside
that's already chewed, like the way mommy used to do it
Enough!
Until I turned 12 years old
and she's like "Chew your own food"
And I said, "No, I do not like it"
Most annoying creature ever to cross my path
Can you let the dragon come out
Take him and go! Please, I beg you!
The Deathgripper will have to forget dinner
You feed your dragons, dragons?!
- Go!
- Where is your bathroom? I gotta...
Okay, Gods, no wonder you have grey hair
Stress is not good for you
So long losers!
Where, where is she heading?
She is tracking something
Aren't you girl?
There is nothing but miles and miles of...
- A wide waterfall
- At the end of the world
Stormfly!
It really does exists!
- Toothless!
- You'll spook them.
Now That's the King
We should go
Oh no
Firefly!
Down! Go!
I'm sorry, but but, I can exp...
Son!
- You should be asleep
- I was thirsty
Yeah! Come here
Dad!?
Are you gonna get us a new mom?
I don't want another. Your mom!
Was the only woman for me
And she was all love of my life
But with love comes loss, son
That's part of the deal
Sometimes it hurts, but in the end
its all worth it
There is no better gift than love
It's okay, bud!
You belong there, with her
We don't
And that's alright
We'll find a way to man
Hey!
She followed us back
We might not have to say goodbye after all
That's it!
- Ruffnut
- Miss me
How did you escape?
I annoyed them until they let me go
Wait! Grimmel let you go?!
So dumb. They couldn't handle me
See everyone thinks Tuffnut is more annoying, but
- Hold on
- Ruffnut, focus. Were you followed?
I never looked back, Hiccup
Toothless!
Toothless, come back!
No!
Now, our little game must come to an end
Call them off Alpha
No reason for her to die to
What are you doing?
They can totally take him!
Not with her life on the line
Save your breath
The only Alpha they respond to is me
Don't feel too badly.
You've tried your best
But you're nothing without your dragon
Toothless!
Now that is just... Great!
Now What?
I think it's time for
number 2 to become number 1
He'll listen to you
- Don't say it
- I wasn't going to
I should have dragged you out there
He wouldn't have flown me back.
She wouldn't have followed
Yeap
I feel like the same screwed-up
I was before I met Toothless
I can see that
Are you just gonna stand there
and agree with everything?!
Well, You're right,
you're back to where you started
But I was the first to believe in you
And I have watched you doubt
whether you're worthy ever since
But you know what
I am the person I am today because of you
I never told you that, but it's true
You are the bravest, most stubborn,
most determined
knuckle-head I know
Toothless didn't give you that, Hiccup!
- He just made it
- Easier
And now it gonna be a lot harder
So, what are you gonna do about it?
Probably something stupid
That's the Hiccup I know
Suit up gang! We're going to get them back!
What?
He's lost his mind
Now that's marriage material
At last, faithful people, you're ready
How are we gonna get our dragons back?
- Without dragons
- Trust me
Move!
That's right, Alpha
No surprises
Jump off the cliff in these
- That's the best you've got
- No
You guys are the best I've got
I'm with him! Who else?
Thats was my line.
Let's go!
Yes!
You didn't think I would actually
hand you the Night Fury did you?
He's mine to kill
That Snake
I intend to finish what I've started
Best of luck controlling them without an Alpha
Hold on Toothless!
Could have used some perculations to skip breakfast
Toothless!
Perfect timing!
Game Faces
Good boy! Get in there!
Heads up!
Thanks, look out!
Thanks!
I'm coming Toothless!
You still think he cares about you
Let's just see who he follows
I'm sorry bud, for everything
Let's go get her
Yeah! Number 2 Coming through
Surprise!
Sorry about that
Come On!
One more free, 4 to go
Try To keep up!
I'll got your backs
Yeah! Its almost like we're a team
You brought a baby to a battle
I wouldn't do that if I were you
God! I love that dragon
- Sorry we're late for the party
- You're right on time
That's it! That's it!
How do we get him off her back without hearting her?
Fear the facial hair!
- I have missed this
- Me too!
- See that there
- Cute!
That's a bad omen. You're cursed
Yes! Go! Good on you!
I Guess your not so bad after all
Leave the ship!
We got problems!
Get him, Hiccup!
We need a better plan
and quick!
Bat guy! What are you doing?
Ok! Ok!
You're killing both of us!
Fighting over a dragon. That's your plan?!
This is
Save him
See! I knew you've come around
Hey, good morning bud
Here you go
All you full of surprises
He's all yours
You know Eret may be blessed with brawl but
just between us, you have the brains
No. 1
You're right, bud. It's time
I was so busy, fighting for a world that I wanted
I didn't think about what you needed
You've looked after us for long enough
Time to look after yourselves
Stormfly, my good girl
All right Grumply
Of you go
So long, you bigerbly beast. I'll miss you
Cloudjumper
Go on, bud!
Lead them to the hidden world
You will be safe there
Safer than you could ever be with me
It's okay, I love you too and
I want you to be free
Our world does not deserve you
Yet
Go Toothless
Go
For chief and the chieftess
Yeah
Come, cry to my full thick beard
Give me a hug
Gross
Okay, you win
I like sensitive guys
There were dragons when I was a boy
There were great grim sky dragons
that nested at the cliff tops
like gigantic scary birds
little brown scadily dragons,
that hunted down the mice and rats
and well organised packs
Preposterously huge sea dragons that were
20 times as big as the big blue whale
Some say they crawl back into the sea leaving
not a bone not a fang from men to remember them by
Other say they were nothing but folk tales to begin with
I'm okay with that!
Hey, hey there bud
Remember me
Its ok
It's glad to see you too
He's not gonna eat your father
How is your tail holding up
Do you want to see me do a little bit more fine tuning
Its ok, they're friends
Come here. Come on,
Go on, its alright
He won't hurt you
Hold your hands out, like this
That's it
Let him come to you
The legend says, that when the ground quakes
or lava spews from the earth, its the dragons
Letting us know their still here
Waiting for us to figure out how to get along
Yes
The world believes that the dragons are gone
if they ever existed at all
But we Berkin's we know otherwise
And we'll guard the secret until the time comes
when the dragon can return in peace